<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-12-17T01:21:12-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Lard News [Archive]</title><subtitle>Former website of Lard News, the Lardish Government news agency. It has been archived due to the dissolution of the Lardish Republic effective on December 31, 2024.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">[BREAKING NEWS] Lardish Republic dissolved by the President</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/12/16/breaking-news-lardish-republic-dissolved-by-the-president/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[BREAKING NEWS] Lardish Republic dissolved by the President" /><published>2024-12-16T14:19:05-06:00</published><updated>2024-12-16T14:19:05-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/12/16/breaking-news-lardish-republic-dissolved-by-the-president</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/12/16/breaking-news-lardish-republic-dissolved-by-the-president/"><![CDATA[<p>CLD, USFLR – Monday, December 16, 2024.</p>

<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The President of the Republic released a televised speech at 6:00 AM (CLT). In that speech, he announced his resignation from his position and ‘any political duties’ and, most shockingly, the dissolution of the Lardish Republic. He thanked his supporters and all citizens of the Republic, but as he said, “All good things must come to an end.”</span></p>

<p>You can find it <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O1fXNl-qjR0&amp;pp=ygUUdGhlIGxhcmRpc2ggcmVwdWJsaWM%3D">here</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>admin</name></author><category term="Breaking News" /><category term="National News" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLD, USFLR – Monday, December 16, 2024.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[BREAKING NEWS] President expected to resign</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/12/09/breaking-news-president-expected-to-resign/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[BREAKING NEWS] President expected to resign" /><published>2024-12-09T00:10:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-12-09T00:10:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/12/09/breaking-news-president-expected-to-resign</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/12/09/breaking-news-president-expected-to-resign/"><![CDATA[<p>Palace of Lowx, Tard – Monday, December 09, 2024.</p>

<p>Insider information obtained from the Presidential Cabinet of the United States of the First Lardish Republic indicates that the President’s resignation is imminent, as reported by our journalists. They were invited to a press conference scheduled for tomorrow at the President’s official residence on December 10.</p>

<p>According to the insider’s report, the President is currently grappling with personal matters and was unanimously endorsed by his team to step down. He was re-elected President in the 2023 General Elections, defeating Mrs. Yuyu’s candidacy. He was inaugurated into office on January 20, 2024, and his term is scheduled to conclude on January 19, 2028.</p>

<p>The President’s approval rating remains exceptionally high, with 92% of the Lardish population expressing satisfaction with his leadership and the country’s management. Recently, he proposed constitutional amendments, which were approved in a historic bipartisan agreement.</p>

<p>However, it remains uncertain whether the President will resign or not. If he does, the succession process will be challenging, as the country faces internal divisions that could hinder the selection of a suitable leader.</p>]]></content><author><name>admin</name></author><category term="Breaking News" /><category term="National News" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palace of Lowx, Tard – Monday, December 09, 2024.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">President releases press release with the official results of the plenary session of the Central Lardish Committee</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/12/06/president-releases-press-release-with-the-official-results-of-the-plenary-session-of-the-central-lardish-committee/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="President releases press release with the official results of the plenary session of the Central Lardish Committee" /><published>2024-12-06T19:15:21-06:00</published><updated>2024-12-06T19:15:21-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/12/06/president-releases-press-release-with-the-official-results-of-the-plenary-session-of-the-central-lardish-committee</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/12/06/president-releases-press-release-with-the-official-results-of-the-plenary-session-of-the-central-lardish-committee/"><![CDATA[<p>CLD, USFLR – Friday, December 06, 2024.</p>

<p>Following the plenary session of the Central Lardish Committee to vote on the proposed constitutional amendments, the President was expected to deliver the results through a televised speech on November 30. However, he didn’t release any speech.</p>

<p>Two days ago, on December 04, he briefly shared the overall results with Lard News and other news chains but not the individual results per party or coalition.</p>

<p>In a press release today, Lard Lapudding announced the detailed voting breakdown and officially delivered the results to the Lardish Government.</p>

<p>Lard News was provided with the press release and you can find it here: <a href="/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Official-results-CLC.pdf">Official results CLC</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>admin</name></author><category term="Breaking News" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLD, USFLR – Friday, December 06, 2024.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">President talks on the result in the CLC of the proposed bill that amends the PC</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/12/04/president-talks-on-the-result-in-the-clc-of-the-proposed-bill-that-amends-the-pc/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="President talks on the result in the CLC of the proposed bill that amends the PC" /><published>2024-12-04T15:28:59-06:00</published><updated>2024-12-04T15:28:59-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/12/04/president-talks-on-the-result-in-the-clc-of-the-proposed-bill-that-amends-the-pc</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/12/04/president-talks-on-the-result-in-the-clc-of-the-proposed-bill-that-amends-the-pc/"><![CDATA[<p>CLD, USFLR – December 04, 2024.</p>

<p>Last Friday, the plenary session of the Central Lardish Committee that decided the result of the amendment of the Political Constitution was held. The President has shared with Lard News the results.</p>

<p>With 51 votes in favor and 13 votes against, the proposal has passed, meeting the required majority of 33 votes (50% + 1) in the event of a proposed amendment to the Constitution.</p>

<p>“The approval of this bill demonstrates the Committee’s commitment to serving the evolving needs and values of the Lardish Republic and its people”, Lard Lapudding said in his video addressing Lard News and the country.</p>

<p>The amendments will come into effect, at the latest, on January 01<sup>st</sup>, 2025.</p>]]></content><author><name>admin</name></author><category term="National News" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLD, USFLR – December 04, 2024.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Projected results from the Central Lardish Committee</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/11/29/projected-results-from-the-central-lardish-committee/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Projected results from the Central Lardish Committee" /><published>2024-11-29T15:02:46-06:00</published><updated>2024-11-29T15:02:46-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/11/29/projected-results-from-the-central-lardish-committee</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/11/29/projected-results-from-the-central-lardish-committee/"><![CDATA[<p>CLD, USFLR – November 29, 2024.</p>

<p>The meeting in the Central Lardish Committee to amend the Political Constitution will be held today at 16:00 (Central Lardish Time) in the Royal Palace of Lowx, Tard. Based on the stance each member has announced, we can project on the results, which will be delivered tomorrow in a televised speech by Lard Lapudding, President of the Republic and spokesperson of the Central Lardish Committee.</p>

<p>Based on the previous results documents, here is the official Lard News projection of the voting results in the Central Lardish Committee for the proposed constitutional amendments.</p>

<h3 id="proposed-amendments"><strong>Proposed Amendments:</strong></h3>

<ol>
  <li>Remove “Lardish” as a National Language.</li>
  <li>Rename the country from “United States of the First Lardish Republic” to “the Lardish Republic”.</li>
</ol>

<h3 id="previous-results"><strong>Previous Results</strong>:</h3>

<ul>
  <li><strong>House of Deputies</strong>: The proposal passed with 122 votes in favor and 82 against, driven by strong support from the CNP coalition, and the Apple Lardish Party.</li>
  <li><strong>Lardish Senate</strong>: The proposal passed with 32 votes in favor and 16 against, reflecting a historic bipartisan agreement, reflecting the compromise of both coalitions.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="coalitions-and-seats-in-the-central-lardish-committee"><strong>Coalitions and Seats in the Central Lardish Committee</strong>:</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Coalition of the Lardish National Party (LNP) and Lardish Fritos National Party (LFNP): 18 seats.</li>
  <li>Coalition of the Colish National Party (CNP) and Lardish People’s Party (LPP): 38 seats.</li>
  <li>Apple Lardish Party (ALP): 8 seats.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="analysis-of-voting-trends"><strong>Analysis of Voting Trends</strong>:</h3>

<h4 id="right-wing-coalition-lnp"><strong>Right-Wing Coalition (LNP)</strong></h4>

<ul>
  <li>At first, they seemed to be resistant to the removal of “Lardish” as a national language but showed partial support for renaming the country, especially after concessions in cultural preservation.</li>
  <li><strong>Projection</strong>: 6 votes in favor, 12 against.</li>
</ul>

<h4 id="liberal-coalition-cnp"><strong>Liberal Coalition (CNP)</strong></h4>

<ul>
  <li>The liberal coalition has supported these amendments in the lower and higher chambers, regardless of being proposed by a president who is a member of the right-wing party. And in the CLC, where the coalition holds a majority, there doesn’t seem to be a game-changing difference.</li>
  <li><strong>Projection</strong>: 38 votes in favor, 0 against.</li>
</ul>

<h4 id="apple-lardish-party"><strong>Apple Lardish Party</strong></h4>

<ul>
  <li>Has shown partial support for the amendment and none of its members have taken a stance.</li>
  <li><strong>Projection</strong>: 6 votes in favor, 2 against.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="projected-voting-results-in-the-central-lardish-committee"><strong>Projected Voting Results in the Central Lardish Committee:</strong></h3>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Total Votes in Favor</strong>: 50.</li>
  <li><strong>Total Votes Against</strong>: 14.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="outcome"><strong>Outcome:</strong></h3>

<p>The proposal is expected to secure <strong><em>50 votes</em></strong>, surpassing the mandated majority of 33 votes (50% + 1) in the event of a Constitutional Amendment or Enactment. The amendments are expected to be approved.</p>

<h3 id="significance"><strong>Significance</strong>:</h3>

<p>This approval demonstrates alignment across the legislative hierarchy and emphasizes the Lardish Republic’s commitment to reflecting its evolving identity and compromise to move away from its “dark past”. Despite some conservative resistance, the process highlighted bipartisan collaboration.</p>

<p><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Projection-Outcome-CLC-Nov2924-300x191.png" alt="" /></p>]]></content><author><name>admin</name></author><category term="National News" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLD, USFLR – November 29, 2024.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Projection-Outcome-CLC-Nov2924.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Projection-Outcome-CLC-Nov2924.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Central Lardish Committee plenary session date announced</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/11/27/central-lardish-committee-plenary-session-date-announced/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Central Lardish Committee plenary session date announced" /><published>2024-11-27T23:59:43-06:00</published><updated>2024-11-27T23:59:43-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/11/27/central-lardish-committee-plenary-session-date-announced</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/11/27/central-lardish-committee-plenary-session-date-announced/"><![CDATA[<p>CLD, USFLR – November 27, 2024.</p>

<p>The Central Lardish Committee has announced through their spokesperson that their next plenary session will be held on Friday, November 29, 2024. The session will review the bill that would amend the Constitution, following its approval in the Senate and House of Deputies. For the bill to be passed, it does not require the typical 38 members-approved majority, as it is a constitutional amendment; instead, it requires at least 2/3 of the total membership of the Committee to be present, and the amendment would require 50% + 1 members of the total membership, so it would only need to secure 33 votes in favor. Furthermore, the left-wing and the right-wing coalitions, as well as the centrist Apple Lardish Party have expressed their support for the bill, therefore, its approval is expected by many analysts. If approved, it would mark a historic milestone in Lardish history and would allow the President to fulfill his campaign promises. As it currently stands, the left-wing coalition of the Colish National Party and the Lardish People’s Party has the approved majority on the Committee, and all of its members have promised that they would vote in favor; similarly, the Lardish National Party has expressed their willingness to help the President on achieving his goals for the well-being of the Lardish citizens. The Lardish Fritos National Party has not spoken on this issue, and insider information suggests that the party is split, the more radical conservatives have openly opposed the bill as it would destroy Lardish heritage, whereas the centrist-leaning members of the LFNP have divided opinions, but are expected to vote in favor.</p>

<p><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-28-at-12.03.58 PM-300x232.png" alt="" /></p>]]></content><author><name>admin</name></author><category term="National News" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLD, USFLR – November 27, 2024.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-28-at-12.03.58%E2%80%AFPM.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-28-at-12.03.58%E2%80%AFPM.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">[BREAKING NEWS] Historic Bipartisan Agreement reached in the Senate</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/11/24/breaking-news-historic-bipartisan-agreement-reached-in-the-senate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[BREAKING NEWS] Historic Bipartisan Agreement reached in the Senate" /><published>2024-11-24T14:49:03-06:00</published><updated>2024-11-24T14:49:03-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/11/24/breaking-news-historic-bipartisan-agreement-reached-in-the-senate</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/11/24/breaking-news-historic-bipartisan-agreement-reached-in-the-senate/"><![CDATA[<p>CLD, USFLR – November 23, 2024.</p>

<p>In a plenary session, the Lardish Senate approved the bill to amend the Political Constitution of the United States of the First Lardish Republic (PCOTUSFLR), marking a significant step toward modernizing the nation’s legal framework. The bill, which required 28 votes to pass, secured 32 votes in favor and 16 against, thanks to a historic bipartisan agreement.</p>

<p>The bill addresses two key issues:</p>

<ol>
  <li>The removal of “Lardish” as a national language.</li>
  <li>Renaming the country from “United States of the First Lardish Republic” to “the Lardish Republic.”</li>
</ol>

<p>Here are the results obtained, according to the spokesperson of the Senate, Alexa Correa:</p>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Coalition of the Lardish National Party and Lardish Fritos National Party (28 seats):</strong>
    <ul>
      <li>Votes in favor: 14</li>
      <li>Votes against: 14</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li><strong>Coalition of the Colish National Party and Lardish People’s Party (18 seats):</strong>
    <ul>
      <li>Votes in favor: 16</li>
      <li>Votes against: 2</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li><strong>Apple Lardish Party (2 seats):</strong>
    <ul>
      <li>Votes in favor: 2</li>
      <li>Votes against: 0</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li><strong>Total votes in favor:</strong> 32</li>
  <li><strong>Total votes against:</strong> 16</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="voting-breakdown">Voting Breakdown:</h3>

<p>The liberal coalition overwhelmingly supported the amendments, citing them as vital steps toward inclusivity and modernization, however, the conservative coalition seemed hesitant at first, as previously seen in the House of Deputies, nevertheless, after extensive negotiations, half of the conservative coalition supported the bill, contingent on assurances that cultural heritage would be honored through initiatives like a national historical institute. The Apple Lardish Party fully backed the amendments, emphasizing their balanced approach to progress and tradition.</p>

<h3 id="what-are-the-next-steps">What are the Next Steps?</h3>

<p>The Senate’s approval follows the bill’s successful passage in the House of Deputies, where it also garnered the required majority. The proposal will now proceed to the Central Lardish Committee, the only body authorized to amend and enact the constitution. The CLC is expected to review the amendments, at the latest, by December 6, 2024.</p>

<h3 id="public-reactions">Public Reactions</h3>

<p>“This moment of bipartisan cooperation has been hailed as a victory for unity and progress. While some nationalist conservatives expressed concerns about preserving historical identity, the agreement reflects a shared commitment to addressing the evolving needs of our beautiful nation”, expressed Lard Lapudding in a press release.</p>

<p>These amendments signify a new chapter in the nation’s journey, balancing its rich heritage with the demands of a modern, inclusive society. All that is left is the final verdict from the Central Committee.</p>]]></content><author><name>admin</name></author><category term="Breaking News" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLD, USFLR – November 23, 2024.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[BREAKING NEWS] Proposal to amend the Constition passed in the House of Deputies.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/11/15/breaking-news-proposal-to-amend-the-constition-passed-in-the-house-of-deputies/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[BREAKING NEWS] Proposal to amend the Constition passed in the House of Deputies." /><published>2024-11-15T16:04:07-06:00</published><updated>2024-11-15T16:04:07-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/11/15/breaking-news-proposal-to-amend-the-constition-passed-in-the-house-of-deputies</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/11/15/breaking-news-proposal-to-amend-the-constition-passed-in-the-house-of-deputies/"><![CDATA[<p>CLD, USFLR – Lard Lapudding, President of the USFLR, acting on his duties as spokesperson of the Lardish House of Deputies, recently released the voting results on the proposal to amend Articles 1 and 38. The proposed bill includes the removal of Lardish as a national language and changing the country’s name from “the United States of the First Lardish Republic” to “the Lardish Republic”. He and his team proposed the bill at the beginning of this week, and today, Friday, November 15, 2024, it was received by the House of Deputies. The Lardish National Party, of which the current President is part, strongly opposed the bill, meaning that there is starting to be some division among his party. Overall, the results per party are as follows:</p>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Coalition of the Lardish National Party and Lardish Fritos National Party (106 seats)</strong>:
    <ul>
      <li>Votes in favor: 40</li>
      <li>Votes against: 66</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li><strong>Coalition of the Colish National Party and Lardish People’s Party (82 seats)</strong>:
    <ul>
      <li>Votes in favor: 72</li>
      <li>Votes against: 10</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li><strong>Apple Lardish Party (16 seats)</strong>:
    <ul>
      <li>Votes in favor: 10</li>
      <li>Votes against: 6</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
</ul>

<p>The bill required at least 120 votes for approval. With a total of 122 votes in favor and 82 against, the proposal has successfully passed in the House of Deputies and will now be passed onto the Lardish Senate, on which if it passes, it will become a law.</p>

<p>You can find the letter submitted by the President indicating the results here.</p>

<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Result-of-the-proposal-to-amend-the-Constitution-in-the-House-of-Deputies.pdf">Result of the proposal to amend the Constitution in the House of Deputies</a></p>]]></content><author><name>admin</name></author><category term="Breaking News" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLD, USFLR – Lard Lapudding, President of the USFLR, acting on his duties as spokesperson of the Lardish House of Deputies, recently released the voting results on the proposal to amend Articles 1 and 38. The proposed bill includes the removal of Lardish as a national language and changing the country’s name from “the United States of the First Lardish Republic” to “the Lardish Republic”. He and his team proposed the bill at the beginning of this week, and today, Friday, November 15, 2024, it was received by the House of Deputies. The Lardish National Party, of which the current President is part, strongly opposed the bill, meaning that there is starting to be some division among his party. Overall, the results per party are as follows:]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Press release</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/10/01/press-release/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Press release" /><published>2024-10-01T13:38:08-06:00</published><updated>2024-10-01T13:38:08-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/10/01/press-release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/10/01/press-release/"><![CDATA[<p>CLD, USFLR – The Central Lardish Committee has released a list of the newly appointed Ministers of State.</p>

<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/General-Announcement.pdf">General Announcement</a></p>]]></content><author><name>admin</name></author><category term="National News" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLD, USFLR – The Central Lardish Committee has released a list of the newly appointed Ministers of State.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">[BREAKING NEWS] New Prime Minister Appointed</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/09/21/breaking-news-new-prime-minister-appointed/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[BREAKING NEWS] New Prime Minister Appointed" /><published>2024-09-21T00:34:02-06:00</published><updated>2024-09-21T00:34:02-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/09/21/breaking-news-new-prime-minister-appointed</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/09/21/breaking-news-new-prime-minister-appointed/"><![CDATA[<p>CLD, USFLR – The Lardish Government has finally appointed a new Prime Minister, after Juana Banana’s resignation earlier this year in July. The appointment of the country’s second-most-important person in the Presidential Cabinet was delayed due to disagreements in the Central Lardish Committee. The deadline for the Central Lardish Committee to approve the proposed PM seat by the current ruling party, the Lardish National Party, was July 10, however, the party couldn’t get an agreement on the CLC, instead, the Colish National Party, the runner-up from the last election, controlling 38 seats in the Committee, the minimum approved majority, decided to appoint Alexa Correa, the loser of the extraordinary elections last year, as the new Prime Minister. This decision was met with severe backlash by the LNP in the House of Representatives, the Deputies House, and the Senate, where the Lardish National Party has a minor majority, which means that they require votes in favor of the CNP or the Apple Lardish Party to propose a bill to the Supreme Constitutional Court to impeach Alexa Correa. The president of the Republic, Lard Lapudding welcomed her to the Presidential Cabinet and he supports the decision of the CLC to appoint her as PM. It is expected that in the following days, the President and the Prime Minister will appoint ministers of state.</p>]]></content><author><name>admin</name></author><category term="Breaking News" /><category term="National News" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[CLD, USFLR – The Lardish Government has finally appointed a new Prime Minister, after Juana Banana’s resignation earlier this year in July. The appointment of the country’s second-most-important person in the Presidential Cabinet was delayed due to disagreements in the Central Lardish Committee. The deadline for the Central Lardish Committee to approve the proposed PM seat by the current ruling party, the Lardish National Party, was July 10, however, the party couldn’t get an agreement on the CLC, instead, the Colish National Party, the runner-up from the last election, controlling 38 seats in the Committee, the minimum approved majority, decided to appoint Alexa Correa, the loser of the extraordinary elections last year, as the new Prime Minister. This decision was met with severe backlash by the LNP in the House of Representatives, the Deputies House, and the Senate, where the Lardish National Party has a minor majority, which means that they require votes in favor of the CNP or the Apple Lardish Party to propose a bill to the Supreme Constitutional Court to impeach Alexa Correa. The president of the Republic, Lard Lapudding welcomed her to the Presidential Cabinet and he supports the decision of the CLC to appoint her as PM. It is expected that in the following days, the President and the Prime Minister will appoint ministers of state.]]></summary></entry></feed>